<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science Slam Zürich</title>
    <link>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Science Slam Zürich</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 20:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://scienceslamzurich.ch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mavi N. Polatoglu</title>
      <link>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/team/mavi-polatoglu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 21:14:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/team/mavi-polatoglu/</guid>
      <description>I am student at ETH Zürich and working part-time in IT&amp;rsquo;IS Foundation in the field of biomedical engineering. Things that excite me are engineering, science, rock &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; roll, and pretty lights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murezi Capaul</title>
      <link>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/team/murezi-capaul/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 21:14:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/team/murezi-capaul/</guid>
      <description>Murezi has been with Science Slam Zurich for about a year. Being the treasurer, he must sometimes play the role of the fun-police. As opposed to the real scientists and engineers in the team, he is still in his health science and technolgy bachelors, looking to get the degree in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benjamin Schneider</title>
      <link>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/team/benjamin-schneider/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 21:14:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/team/benjamin-schneider/</guid>
      <description>Benjamin joined Science Slam Zurich back in 2016 while working in software engineering in the events industry out of a passion for organizing events and learning about new topics. Currently studying Computer Science and Economics in Zurich, he takes care of all online activities and helps producing our events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jens Duru</title>
      <link>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/team/jens-duru/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 21:14:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/team/jens-duru/</guid>
      <description>Jens, 25 - recently graduated from ETH Zurich with a Masters in Biomedical Engineering and is currently trying to do some scijens as a PhD student.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>19.5ᵗʰ Science Slam Zürich - POSTPONED</title>
      <link>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/events/rote-fabrik-slam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/events/rote-fabrik-slam/</guid>
      <description>Due to the current situation of the pandemic, we are forced to postpone this event until further notice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casino Science Slam</title>
      <link>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/events/casino-science-slam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/events/casino-science-slam/</guid>
      <description>Join us at Casino Theatre Wintherthur to witness what happens when science slam meets poetry slam. Our science slam topics are used to inspire poetry slammers and create a whole new flavour. Adding to all of this, the evening will be moderated by the renowned Patti Basler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come Chat with Us at Zurich Life Science Day 2020</title>
      <link>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/events/zurich-life-science-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 08:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/events/zurich-life-science-day/</guid>
      <description>Zurich Life Science Day is the largest career fair dedicated to Life Sciences in Switzerland.
This anual event, organised by the Life Science Zurich Young Scientist Network, takes place at the Lichthof of the University of Zurich, Campus Irchel.
Join us on the 28th of January 2020 and interact with representatives from more than 40 companies, in our company exhibition. Moreover, you have the chance to get your CV chacked and to take a professional CV picture!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressions</title>
      <link>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/static-pages/impressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 08:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/static-pages/impressions/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partners</title>
      <link>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/static-pages/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 08:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://scienceslamzurich.ch/static-pages/partners/</guid>
      <description>General Partners We are thankful for the on-going support of the following organizations, without which our activities would not be possible.
 Current Partners Upcoming Science Slam Zurich events are supported by the following partners.
 Past Partners Past Science Slam Zurich events were supported by the following partners.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>